(Bernadette:)Knock-knock.
Who is there?
(Sheldon:)Hugh.
Hugh who?
(Sheldon:)Hugh people need to
listen to me.
(Sheldon:)It's time to get
in line for the movie.
(Sheldon:)And that's how you tell
a knock-knock joke.
(Sheldon:)Under normal circumstances
I'd say, "I told you so."
(Sheldon:)But as I have told you so
(Sheldon:)with such vehemence
and frequency already,
(Sheldon:)the phrase has lost all meaning.
(Sheldon:)Therefore, I will be
replacing it with the phrase:
"I informed you thusly."
(Howard:)Ooh. Can't wait
for that to start.
(Sheldon:)I informed you thusly.
(Raj:)Eight for 28.
(Sheldon:)This is where we could have been
if we hadn't stopped for dinner.
(Sheldon:)if Koothrappali
hadn't ordered dessert.
(Raj:)Well I earned it, dude,
I ate all my broccoli.
(Sheldon:)And here's where we are.
The runts in a large litter.